There is no way of finding a single absolute truth
The Oxford Murders is a crime, mystery, thriller
film directed by Álex de la Iglesia.
At Oxford University, a professor and a grad student work together to try and stop a
potential series of murders seemingly linked by mathematical symbols.
Martin, played by Elijah Wood.
Arthur Seldom, played by John Hurt.
Lorna, played by Leonor Watling.
Beth, played by Julie Cox.
Inspector Petersen, played by Jim Carter.
Kalman, played by Alex Cox.
The Oxford Murders is a 2008 thriller drama film co-written and directed by Álex de la
Iglesia and starring Elijah Wood, John Hurt, Leonor Watling and Julie Cox.
It is based on 2003's novel of the same name by Argentine
mathematician and writer Guillermo Martínez.
The film explores themes of philosophy, mathematics,
mathematician, symbolism, oxford.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.